{
    "subject": "Chulalongkorn",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Saovabha_Bongsri",
    "human_readable": "Chulalongkorn is married to Saovabha Bongsri.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9829500913619995,
            "question": "Is there a relationship between Chulalongkorn and Saovabha Bongsri?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9517065286636353,
            "question": "To whom is Chulalongkorn married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9473106265068054,
            "question": "Is Chulalongkorn married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9419375061988831,
            "question": "Name the spouse of Chulalongkorn."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9215003252029419,
            "question": "Who is married to Saovabha Bongsri?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9090698957443237,
            "question": "Who is Saovabha Bongsri married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8219747543334961,
            "question": "What is the name of Chulalongkorn's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8117133975028992,
            "question": "Who is Chulalongkorn?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7870222330093384,
            "question": "What is the marital status of Chulalongkorn?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7796922922134399,
            "question": "Can you tell me the names of Chulalongkorn and his spouse?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Chulalongkorn is married to Saovabha Bongsri.",
            "html": "yago_2898_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the marital status of Chulalongkorn?",
            "html": "yago_2898_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Chulalongkorn?",
            "html": "yago_2898_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Chulalongkorn's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_2898_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2898_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2898_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2898_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2898_139.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2898_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2898_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2898_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2898_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2898_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2898_77.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents contain multiple references to Queen Saovabha Bongsri being the wife of King Chulalongkorn, which supports the triple."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about King Chulalongkorn (Rama V) and his wife, Queen Saovabha Phongsri (also known as Saovabha Bongsri), which supports the statement that Chulalongkorn is married to Saovabha Bongsri."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}